pixer.mobi 2013-06-20

# 

PRIVACY POLICY OVERVIEW

This overview serves to to give you (“User”) an overall understanding of Pixer’s (“we”, “our”),  information collection and use practices. Please read the full Privacy Policy for the full explanation of our privacy practices.

We collect information which:

\- you provide when you register for and set up an account

\- you post or share on Pixer

\- you allow social media services (e.g., Facebook, Twitter) to share with us

\- we get from seeing how you use Pixer

\- we get from communicating with you

\- we get from cookies and other technology

We use this information to:

\- provide Pixer features and services to you

\- manage and improve Pixer

\- analyze how you use Pixer

\- provide you with information

\- diagnose technical problems and maintain security

We share this information with:

\- other Pixer users

\- social media services you tell us to share information with

\- people and organizations who help us provide Pixer to you

\- business partners, which may include advertising partners

\- outside parties to comply with the law and legal obligations

PRIVACY POLICY

Effective date: January 1, 2013.

This Privacy Policy explains how Pixer collects, uses, shares and protects information, and your choices about the collection and use of your information.

By using Pixer you understand and agree that we are providing a platform for you to post content, including photos, comments and other materials ("User Content"), to Pixer and to share User Content publicly. This means that other Users may search for, see, use, or share any of your User Content that you make publicly available through Pixer, consistent with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use.

**1\. INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

We collect the following types of information:

Information you provide us directly:

Profile information that you provide to us directly or via social media networks (e.g., Facebook, Twitter), including your name, username, email address, profile picture.

User Content (e.g., photos, comments, and other materials) that you post to Pixer.

Communications between you and Pixer. For example, we may send you emails (e.g., account verification, changes/updates to features of Pixer, technical and security notices).

Finding other Pixer users:

If you choose, you can use a feature to locate other people with Pixer accounts either through your contacts list, or third-party social media sites.

If you choose to find other users through your device's contacts list, then Pixer will access your contacts list to determine whether or not someone associated with your contact is using Pixer.

If you choose to find other users through a third-party social media site, then you will be prompted to set up a link to the third-party service and you understand that any information that such service may provide to us will be governed by this Privacy Policy.

Note about sending invitations: You may choose to invite someone from your device’s contact list to Pixer via a text message or email. You understand and agree that you are responsible for any charges that apply to communications sent from your device, and because this invitation is coming directly from your personal account, Pixer does not have access to or control this communication.

Analytics information:

We use third-party analytics tools to help us measure traffic and usage trends. These tools collect information sent by your device or Pixer, including the web pages you visit, add-ons, and other information that assists us in improving Pixer. We collect and use this analytics information with analytics information from other Users so that it cannot reasonably be used to identify any particular individual User.

Cookies and similar technologies:

When you visit the Service, we may use cookies and similar technologies like pixels, web beacons, and local storage to collect information about how you use Pixer.

We may ask advertisers or other partners to serve ads or services to your devices, which may use cookies or similar technologies placed by us or the third party.

Log file information:

Log file information is automatically reported by your browser each time you make a request to access (i.e., visit) a web page or app. It can also be provided when the content of the webpage or app is downloaded to your browser or device.

When you use Pixers, we may record certain log file information, including your web request, IP address, browser type, referring / exit pages and URLs, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, and other such information. We may also collect similar information from emails sent to our Users which then help us track which emails are opened and which links are clicked by recipients. 

Device identifiers:

When you use a mobile device like a tablet or phone to access Pixer, we may access, collect, monitor, store on your device, and/or remotely store one or more "device identifiers." Device identifiers are small data files or similar data structures stored on or associated with your mobile device, which uniquely identify your mobile device. A device identifier may be data stored in connection with the device hardware, data stored in connection with the device's operating system or other software, or data sent to the device by Pixer.

A device identifier may deliver information to us or to a third party partner about how you use Pixer and may help us or others provide reports or personalized content and ads. Some features of the Pixer may not function properly if use or availability of device identifiers is impaired or disabled.

Metadata:

Users can add or may have Metadata added to their User Content including a geotag (e.g., to mark your location to a photo), comments or other data. If you geotag your photo or tag your photo using other's APIs then, your latitude and longitude will be stored with the photo and searchable (e.g., through a location or map feature) if your photo is made public by you in accordance with your privacy settings.

**2\. HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION**

In addition to some of the specific uses of information we describe in this Privacy Policy, we may use information that we receive to:

\- help you efficiently access your information after you sign in

\- remember information so you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit Pixer

\- provide personalized content and information to you and others, which could include online ads or other forms of marketing

\- provide, improve, test, and monitor the effectiveness of Pixer

\- develop and test new products and features

\- monitor metrics such as total number of visitors, traffic, and demographic patterns

\- diagnose or fix technology problems

\- automatically update Pixer on your device

**3\. SHARING OF YOUR INFORMATION**

We will not rent or sell your information to third parties outside Pixer without your consent, except as noted in this Policy.

Parties with whom we may share your information:

We may share your information as well as information from tools like cookies, log files, and device identifiers and location data (such as usage data, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.), with organizations that help us provide Pixer to you ("Service Providers"). Our Service Providers will be given access to your information as is reasonably necessary to provide service under reasonable confidentiality terms.

We may also share certain information such as cookie data with third-party advertising partners. This information would allow third-party ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you.

We may remove parts of data that can identify you and share anonymized data with other parties. We may also combine your information with other information in a way that it is no longer associated with you and share that aggregated information.

Parties with whom you may choose to share your User Content:

Any information or content that you post to the Service, such as User Content, becomes available to the public. Once you have shared User Content or made it public, that User Content may be re-shared by others.

Any User Content is searchable by other Users. 

If you remove information that you posted to Pixer, copies may remain viewable in cached and archived pages, or if other Users or third have copied or saved that information.

What happens in the event of a change of control:

If we sell or otherwise transfer part or the whole of Pixer or our assets to another organization (e.g., in the course of a transaction like a merger, acquisition, bankruptcy, dissolution, liquidation), your information such as name and email address, User Content and any other information collected through the Service may be among the items sold or transferred. You will continue to own your User Content. The buyer or transferee will have to honor the commitments we have made in this Privacy Policy.

Instances where we may be required to share your information:

Pixer will disclose your information where required to do so by law or by judicial process or if we reasonably believe that such action is necessary to:

\- comply with the law and the reasonable requests of law enforcement

\- enforce our Terms of Use

\- protect the security or integrity of our service

\- exercise or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Pixer, our Users or others

**4\. HOW WE STORE YOUR INFORMATION**

Your information collected through Pixer may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Pixer or our Service Providers maintain facilities.

Pixer may transfer information that we collect about you, including personal information across borders and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world. If you are located in the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, please note that we may transfer information, including personal information, to a country and jurisdiction that does not have the same data protection laws as your jurisdiction.

By registering for and using Pixer you consent to the transfer of information to the U.S. or to any other country in which Pixer or our Service Providers maintain facilities and the use and disclosure of information about you as described in this Privacy Policy.

We use commercially reasonable safeguards to help keep the information collected through Pixer secure and take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting you access to your account. However, Pixer cannot ensure the security of any information you transmit to Instagram or guarantee that information on Pixer may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed.

Following termination or deactivation of your account, Pixer may retain information (including your profile information) and User Content for a commercially reasonable time for backup, archival, and/or audit purposes.

**5\. CHILDREN'S PRIVACY**

Pixer does not knowingly collect or solicit any information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register for the service. Pixer and its content are not directed at children under the age of 13. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at support@pixer.mobi

**8\. CONTACT**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the Service, please contact us at support@....

**9\. CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

Pixer may modify or update this Privacy Policy from time to time, so please review it periodically. We may provide you additional forms of notice of modifications or updates as appropriate under the circumstances. Your continued use of Pixer after any modification to this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such modification.
